mbfashionweek.com 2018-12-27

# Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week

This is the Privacy Policy for http://mbfashionweek.com (referred to in this Privacy Policy as this “Site”).

This Site is owned by IMG Fashion, Division of IMG Worldwide, Inc. (referred to in this Privacy Policy as “IMG”). Please direct any questions or comments concerning the Privacy Policy below and the [Terms of Use](http://img.com/Terms-of-Use.aspx) to _[legal@img.com](mailto:legal@img.com)_. PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE SITE’S TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE.

Your privacy is of great importance to IMG. Because IMG gathers certain types of information about the users of this Site, IMG feels you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for this Site with regard to what information IMG gathers, how IMG uses the information, and how you can correct or change the information captured. This Privacy Policy only addresses use of this Site. Third party websites (including those to which this Site links and other websites or service providers with which IMG may have relationships) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which IMG does not control, and IMG is not responsible for nor does IMG endorse such practices or policies.

##  General Privacy Information

This Site contains links to partners, advertisers and third party internet sites and services who may collect data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, e-commerce, etc. They each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of this Site and IMG has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

Please keep in mind that whenever you browse, use, and voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information on any online service or website, including this Site (for example, your name or email address), that information can and will be collected and used by third parties. In short, if you provide information when online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Further, while IMG takes reasonable steps to protect your information using the security and other measures set forth herein, IMG cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information you provide to IMG (if any), and you do so at your own risk. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

##  Collection and Use of Information

This Site collects information about you both from what you provide to IMG and what IMG collects through the use of cookies ( _see_ Cookies below). Information collected about you is used in 2 different ways. (1) Information is "aggregated" -- meaning that the information provided by users of this Site is grouped together in a way that does not disclose the personal information of any particular user. IMG may use this aggregated information to determine user traffic statistics for this Site (including without limitation to determine page visits, duration of stay, the referring URL, IP address geographical location, etc.) and to evaluate which Site content is successful and what is not, and in order to evaluate which content that IMG should make available on this Site. IMG may use only the anonymous click stream data to help IMG and the Site’s advertisers and sponsors deliver better targeted advertisements. In addition, IMG may use information collected through cookies to target e-commerce promotions and marketing activities for products and services related to IMG and/or its clients, sponsors, advertisers and business partners. In addition, some of your information may be shared with third parties who assist IMG in producing content for the Site or provide a service to this Site’s users.

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for IMG to disclose your information. IMG may also disclose information about you if it is determined that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. Additionally, in the event of reorganization, merger, or sale of all or part of its assets, IMG may transfer any and all information collected to the relevant third party.

##  Children Under 13

This Site is a general audience website. On this Site, IMG does not currently knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If, in the future, IMG collects personally identifiable information from children on the Site, IMG will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) including, without limitation, obtaining necessary parental consent. If IMG learns that it has collected the personal information of a child under age 13, IMG will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

##  Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit their website. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that that website uses to track the pages you visit. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to you that has no meaning outside the assigning website. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. This random number lets IMG keep track of how many times users of this Site do specific things - like visiting the Site each month - without really knowing who those users are by name. IMG uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. You must be aware that this Site cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information placed by advertisers or third parties hosting data for this Site. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies maybe necessary to provide you with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on this Site

##  Security

This Site utilizes a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your information. All users contact information is contained behind a "firewall" and only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to production systems. Passwords and credit card numbers are encrypted in this Site's secure database, which is also located behind a firewall. All sensitive/credit information supplied by users is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted in this Site’s databases as stated above. IMG’s security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

##  California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits this Site’s users who are California residents to request certain information regarding IMG’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to _[legal@img.com](mailto:legal@img.com)_.

©2014. IMG Fashion/IMG Worldwide, Inc. All rights reserved.

Last Updated on 04/04/14
